The world.
What a glorious place.
Seek freedom, and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit,
seize it, raise your flag, and stand tall.
I think back to the time
when my search first began.
I left behind those shores of sand.
For the endless,
everlasting world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me.
Someday, somewhere, I'll finally see the
light I have searched for everywhere?.
When the summer sun is shining.
Shaking the sails of my heart. I know.
A brand new world that has been hiding.
Has opened up its doors for me to go.
A way from the moon sky.
Wearing in the troubled waves.
From all despair I can be saved.
For the horizon on the other side is.
And though I travel far
from where my search began.
Over streets of green and shores of sand.
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me.
Some days somewhere I'll finally see
the light I will search for everywhere?.
Oh! Oh!
Oh!
What they got is lucky! So what?
We're just gonna sit
here and let him escape?
We just lost 160 million Barry
Bounty, and you're laughing about it?
Come on, we gotta do something!
Easy, Burgess.
They haven't left this world.
They'll be back.
We'll meet them soon enough, as long as
we stay on the Grand Line. This is true.
We are but cogs in the gears of fate,
and though they've managed to escape
us today, they cannot outrun destiny.
You see, Burgess?
Ah, whatever.
What the...
What just happened to us?
Everyone all right?
Hey, look guys out there! What is that?
What in the world?
It's solid white!
They're clouds! But how?
Why aren't we falling?
Clouds float, boats float, same thing!
No, it's not!
Oh no!
Usopp's not breathing!
He's not!
Someone do something mouth-to-mouth!
Right!
I'll do mouth-to-mouth on Nami! Moron!
Usopp, come on, speak to me!
He's alive!
I am?
Then where are we?
What's with all these clouds?
They're everywhere!
Basically, it's an ocean in
the sky. No way! Seriously?
But look, the Log Pose
is still pointing up.
So we must still be somewhere in the
middle of the cumulo regalus cloud.
Wait, you mean we have
to travel even higher?
That's what the Log Pose says, at least.
Did I hear you call me a moron?
I don't know, did ya? An ocean!
Here I go! No!
Cloud Ocean Swimming Champ, Usopp!
You can't swim here.
We still don't know
anything about this place.
Watch me!
It's hard to see anything,
but I'm really moving.
There's so little resistance.
Wow, I'm just going deeper and deeper.
It's so easy!
Hey, uh, he's not coming back up.
You know it's possible.
This ocean may not have an actual bottom.
Say what? Idiot!
Did that fool just fall
through the clouds?
Stop!
I just told him not to go in there.
Luffy, stretch out as far as you can.
I am, but I can't see where he is.
Just leave that part to me.
Ojos fleurs!
There he is! What? Where?
Vente fleurs!
Okay, now pull him up.
All right, I got him!
Is he heavy?
He shouldn't be that heavy.
Come on, Luffy!
Pull harder!
Yes! He's back!
But he's not alone!
They're trying to eat him! Ah!
You hungry? Eat this!
This air, it's so thin.
It's hard to breathe.
What do you make of this?
It's the strangest
creature I've ever seen.
I'm not even sure it's a fish.
That octopus thing was
more like a big balloon.
Yeah, except balloons don't have teeth.
But how can there be fish
up here in the clouds?
You said it best yourself.
Basically, it's an ocean in the sky.
So what's this big snake thing?
I don't know. A flatfish?
But it wasn't flat until Sanji kicked it.
Oh, come on, Nusof.
What is it this time?
There's something in my pants!
Sky Island's scary.
Not his day.
Hold on.
Do you know what this is?
I think it's one of the skyfish
Nolan described in his law.
It sounded pretty fantastic at
the time, but now that I see it,
It looks like these creatures have somehow
actually evolved to survive
up here in the clouds.
They evolved?
You mean they turned off
flat and Balloon and stuff?
To make themselves even lighter.
The buoyancy up here must be several times
weaker than in the oceans down below.
And they grew scales like feathers
and those weird carnivore-like mouths.
I tried sautéing it. Delicious! Hey!
We were still examining that!
What were you guys thinking?
Wait, this is good.
I've never tasted anything like it.
Well, you know me. I aim to please.
Oh, let's eat the big one.
So where's this Sky Island?
Huh?
What's that?
A ship.
Hey, guys, there's a...
Say, what's wrong, Chopper?
What's the deal?
You see something out there?
Yeah! A ship!
It was there, but then it split!
Say what?
And there's a bull with wings!
And he's running around in the clouds!
You're talking crazy, calm down.
What got into him?
Check it out, he's right.
There's a guy running around out there.
Hey, stop, what do you want?
To destroy you!
Oh, is that all? He's mine.
Who is? What's going on?
Hey, don't let that guy
walk all over you, get him!
Ah!
He's gonna blow us up!
Sky Island's scary.
That's enough, villain!
Oh great, now who's this guy?
Miss, you may call me the Sky Knight.
He's gone.
What's going on here?
Who the heck was that guy?
And you Could you be any more
worthless? That was pathetic.
You had him outnumbered three to one.
You saved us.
Thanks a lot!
I'm just doing my duty.
This one's on the house.
What gives?
I feel so weak.
Yeah, I could barely move.
It must be because of the thin air. What?
Oh, yeah, almost forgot about that.
You must be Blue Sea People.
Blue Sea People? What's that?
And who are you?
As I said, I am the Sky Knight,
and Blue Sea People is what we call
those who live beneath the clouds.
I'm assuming that you've
traveled here from the Blue Sea.
Yeah, that's right.
Then that explains it.
You have reached the White
Sea 7,000 meters in the air.
The White White Sea, where
I assume you're heading,
is still further up, about 10,000 meters.
Ordinary blue sea people
can't possibly endure it here.
Okay, I think I've gotten used to it.
Yeah, I actually feel much better already.
No, no, no, that's just
not possible. So, Mr.
Knight, why was that guy running
around in the clouds attacking people?
Now, now, not so fast.
No doubt you have many questions, but first
we have matters of business to discuss.
Business?
You see, I am a soldier for hire.
The White Seas can be quite dangerous.
There are gorillas lurking about
like the one you've just faced who
would like nothing more than to
turn you into food for the skyfish.
But if you purchase a five million
extol one-whistle, I'll protect you.
What are you talking about?
Now listen, that price
is quite reasonable.
I can't afford to lower
it a single extol more.
I have to earn a living, too.
Yeah, but what the heck is an Stella?
And what's this whistle thing or whatever?
You don't know?
I don't understand.
You came here from the summit
of High West, didn't you?
Surely you must have
passed an island or two.
I still don't know what
you're talking about.
Wait, let me get this straight.
You're saying there's another
way we could have gotten
up here where we would have
passed an island or two?
As in there's more than
one sky island? What?
Don't tell me you traveled by way of...
We rode up on the knock-up stream.
My word, that monstrous current?
So, there are still souls in the world
brave enough to make the attempt.
I knew it, so we risked
our lives for nothing.
Are you happy?
We could have all been killed!
If we just asked around a little more, we
could have found a safer way to get here!
What were you thinking?
Did you lose any of your crew?
No, we all made it.
Then you can consider
yourselves fortunate.
Had you taken a different route, one or
two of you would have survived the journey,
but the rest of you would have perished.
That's the gamble.
By way of the knock-up stream, either
everyone dies or everyone survives.
Those are the only two possible outcomes.
Not many are willing to accept
that sort of all-or-nothing risk,
especially these days.
If nothing else, I see now that you are
navigators of exceptional bravery and skill.
Yeah, well, I hate to take
all the credit, but see?
When things got scary and these guys were
all screaming and crying
for their mommies,
I was the one who stood up and
said, Nothing at all! Thought so.
This is the one whistle.
It is yours to use as you see fit.
Should you find yourselves in danger,
you have but to blow it and
I will come to your aid.
As I said, normally I would charge
you five million extol, but for today,
please accept this as my gift to you.
But wait, we still don't know your name.
I am Gonefall, and this is
my partner, Pierre. Pierre!
Despite appearances,
Pierre is no ordinary bird.
Long ago, he ate of a horse-horse
fruit and gained its powers.
What? What powers?
He is able to transform
into a horse with wings.
Namely...
Oh, wow!
A pegasus!
Yes, a pegasus!
Wow, that's... something.
May luck be with you, brave warriors!
Am I the only one who finds that bizarre?
In the end, he really didn't
tell us anything, did he?
No, nothing, actually.
Well, back to square one, I guess.
Yeah, where are we
supposed to go from here?
I know!
Let's call the old man back and ask him!
Don't even think about it, Luffy!
You don't blow that whistle
to ask for directions!
It's supposed to be for emergencies only!
Yeah!
What if that gorilla guy who
attacked us comes back again?
You want to get blown up?
I'll tell you what, for
now, let's just keep moving.
Hey, look over there, you guys!
What is that?
Some kind of cloud.
It looks more like a waterfall.
Okay, that settles it.
We go that way.
Hey, hold up!
Stop the boat here!
Hmm, looks like the way's blocked.
What do we do?
Those big clouds look like they're
floating on top of the ocean,
sort of like icebergs.
So what, they're cloudbergs?
Well, there's obviously
something different about them.
Maybe I can grab a piece.
Go, go!
Pistol!
It bounced off!
Hey, look!
I'm not sinking!
It's all fluffy and bouncy! It's great!
You guys ought to try this!
Come on, it's fun!
How does this work? It's a
mystery. Woo-hoo! Here I come!
It's going down!
So soft.
It's like a gigantic marshmallow pillow.
Maybe I'll just take a little nap.
Well, we obviously can't
sail through these clouds,
so we'll have to find a way
to get around them somehow.
Hey, you guys see if you can
fly around the ship can take!
Yeah, right!
Luffy, come check this out! What?
Where do you think you're going?
Get back here!
Quit playing around!
What in the world is that? A gate?
Yeah, a big one!
It's up ahead underneath
that waterfall thingy!
So there's a man-made structure
in the middle of the clouds?
At this point, I'm not sure anything
we'd find up here would surprise me.
Well, we'll see soon enough.
Take a left, next.
No, go right.
But it's to our left.
It's on the right.
I'll call the old night guy.
Hey, we're here.
Yep, that's a gate, all right.
And look, that weird cloud we saw
really is some kind of waterfall.
It's coming down on top
of those cloud birds.
Hold on, am I reading this right?
Heaven's Gate?
What's that all about?
Sounds like a place you go when you die.
Yeah, well now that you've
mentioned it, maybe we are dead.
You ever think about that, huh?
Oh, you know that would actually go a long
way towards explaining this weird place.
But I don't want to be dead!
Who cares? We're here, right?
Wherever this gate goes, I'm going.
Will you get fury at you?
What was that for?
If you're making a joke, it's not funny.
So why'd you hit me, too?
Wait, over there.
There's somebody coming out.
Wow, that's what sky people look like.
She's so wrinkly.
State your business.
Sightseeing, warmongering, other.
It makes little difference but if
you wish to proceed you must first
pay the entrance fee of one billion
extol per person that is the law what
what billion they're really big on
these extol things around huh i can't
even count that high i wonder how
much that would be in berries it's
got to be a lot i mean a billion
anything it sounds expensive a billion
per person which makes seven
billion total something's fishy here
seven billion just to go through a
stupid gate i think the old bag's
trying to scam us listen about the
money what if you know we don't have it
you may still pass what
seriously the choice
is yours i certainly won't try to stop you
my job description does not require
me to actually guard the gate i'm
merely here to ask your intentions so
that settles it we want to go to the
sky island but we don't have the money
so we can't pay you very well the
seven of you then yeah except we still
need you to tell us how to get there
the white sea's famous express lobster
Taking us up the waterfall.
Everybody, hang on tight.
It's so fast.
Mrs.
Heaven's Gate, Inspector Amazon.
Hear me now.
To the almighty God above and
his holy priest, I bear tidings.
Seven illegal entrants are
passed into God's land, Skypiea.
Bestow upon them Heaven's Judgment.